dionwired.co.za 2019-05-27

# Dionwired

**Privacy Policy**

As a loyal shopper, you should know DionWired is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy explains how we collect & use customer information. If you have any questions concerning your personal information, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#5d2a383f2e282d2d322f291d393432332a342f3839733e32273c) or 0861 426 323

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website; you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. DionWired may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from regularly to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**Definitions**

“Dionwired” means Masstores (Pty) Ltd (Registration number: 19911971/010815/07), trading as Massdiscounters, a private company with limited liability duly incorporated in the Republic of South Africa.

“Personal information” means information relating to an identifiable, living, natural person and where it is applicable, identifiable, existing juristic person, including all information as defined by the Protection of Personal Information Act 4 of 2013.

“Processing” means the creation, generation. Communication, storage, destruction of personal information as more fully defined in the Protection of Personal Information act 4 of 2013.

“You” or “User” means any person who accesses and browses this website for any purpose.

**Information collected**

DionWired collects the details provided by you on registration together with the information we learn about you from your use of our products or services and the transactions you undertake when visiting our stores and website.

We may collect additional information arising from your participation in promotions, events or competitions offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback or completing forms. We make use of various data enhancement services to ensure that customer data is as accurate as possible. We also recruit new customers through collaborative campaigns with 3rd parties.

We also collect information to ensure that any goods you purchase online are delivered to the correct address and, if there are any issues we are able to contact you or the order recipient to resolve the issue.

We may collect the following information:

  * Name
  * Contact information including email address
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
  * Transactional information
  * Identity number (for TV license validation)

**Use of your Information**

DionWired uses customer information to personalise its service and make communications more relevant to individual customers. This includes direct marketing activities like promotional offers, news and information about products and services that we think will be of interest to customers.

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping
  * We may use the information to improve our product/service offerings to different customer groups based on their interactions

We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. Customers may occasionally also receive very carefully selected and relevant 3rd party communications done in conjunction with ourselves.

Customers are afforded the opportunity to easily opt out of any specific communication channel should they wish to.

From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

DionWired is committed to protecting customer privacy and does not sell or disclose information to anyone for purposes other than as outlined above, unless legally obliged to do so.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes;
  * If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by unsubscribing to our newsletter, emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#fa8d9f98898f8a8a95888eba9e9395948d93889f9ed49995d4809b) or calling us on 0861 426 323.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to 11th Floor North Tower, Liberty towers, 214 Samora Machel Street, Durban, 4001 VAT No: 4300119155.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to (11th Floor North Tower, Liberty towers, 214 Samora Machel Street, Durban, 4001) or email us ([[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#74031116070104041b060034101d1b1a031d0611105a171b5a0e15)) as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**Links to other websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How we use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

**List of cookies we collect**

Below is a list of cookies that we collect and a description of what information they store:

CART - The association with your shopping cart.

CATEGORY_INFO - Stores the category info on the page, which allows displaying pages more quickly.

COMPARE - The items that you have in the Compare Products list.

CURRENCY - Your preferred currency

CUSTOMER - An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.

CUSTOMER_AUTH - An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.

CUSTOMER_INFO - An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.

CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS - Stores the Customer Segment ID

EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE - A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.

FRONTEND - You session ID on the server.

GUEST-VIEW - Allows guests to edit their orders.

LAST_CATEGORY - The last category you visited.

LAST_PRODUCT - The most recent product you have viewed.

NEWMESSAGE - Indicates whether a new message has been received.

NO_CACHE - Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.

PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART - A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.

POLL - The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.

POLLN - Information on what polls you have voted on.

STORE - The store view or language you have selected.

USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE - Indicates whether a customer allowed using cookies.

VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS - The products that you have recently viewed.
